[
    {
        "event": {
            "reo": "reo::Begin_leadership_position",
            "ere": "startposition",
            "lemma": "arrived",
            "propbank": "arrived.XX",
            "mentionid": "em-477",
            "modality": "actual",
            "framenet": "fn::Appointing"
        },
        "arguments": [
            {
                "reo": "reo::Leader",
                "ere": "person",
                "entity": "ent-64",
                "entity-ner": "PER",
                "entity-specificity": "specific",
                "entity-text": "she"
            },
            {
                "reo": "reo::GovernedEntity",
                "ere": "entity",
                "entity": "ent-76",
                "entity-ner": "ORG",
                "entity-specificity": "specific",
                "entity-text": "Senate"
            },
            {
                "reo": "reo::time",
                "ere": "time",
                "entity": "f-509",
                "entity-ner": "time",
                "entity-specificity": "UNK",
                "entity-text": "some three decades ago"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "event": {
            "reo": "reo::Begin_leadership_position",
            "ere": "startposition",
            "lemma": "represented",
            "propbank": "represented.XX",
            "mentionid": "em-542",
            "modality": "actual",
            "framenet": "fn::Appointing"
        },
        "arguments": [
            {
                "reo": "reo::Leader",
                "ere": "person",
                "entity": "ent-112",
                "entity-ner": "PER",
                "entity-specificity": "specific",
                "entity-text": "who"
            },
            {
                "reo": "reo::GovernedEntity",
                "ere": "entity",
                "entity": "ent-100",
                "entity-ner": "ORG",
                "entity-specificity": "specific",
                "entity-text": "U.S. Congress"
            },
            {
                "reo": "reo::time",
                "ere": "time",
                "entity": "f-574",
                "entity-ner": "time",
                "entity-specificity": "UNK",
                "entity-text": "1925"
            },
            {
                "reo": "reo::Position",
                "ere": "position",
                "entity": "f-581",
                "entity-ner": "title",
                "entity-specificity": "UNK",
                "entity-text": "Rep."
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "event": {
            "reo": "reo::End_position_with_organization",
            "ere": "endposition",
            "lemma": "represented",
            "propbank": "represented.XX",
            "mentionid": "em-586",
            "modality": "actual",
            "framenet": "fn::Quitting"
        },
        "arguments": [
            {
                "reo": "reo::Employer",
                "ere": "entity",
                "entity": "ent-100",
                "entity-ner": "ORG",
                "entity-specificity": "specific",
                "entity-text": "U.S. Congress"
            },
            {
                "reo": "reo::Employee",
                "ere": "person",
                "entity": "ent-112",
                "entity-ner": "PER",
                "entity-specificity": "specific",
                "entity-text": "who"
            },
            {
                "reo": "reo::Position",
                "ere": "position",
                "entity": "f-618",
                "entity-ner": "title",
                "entity-specificity": "UNK",
                "entity-text": "Rep."
            },
            {
                "reo": "reo::time",
                "ere": "time",
                "entity": "f-625",
                "entity-ner": "time",
                "entity-specificity": "UNK",
                "entity-text": "1960"
            }
        ]
    },
