[
    {
        "event": {
            "reo": "reo::Marry",
            "ere": "marry",
            "lemma": "wedding",
            "propbank": "wed.01",
            "mentionid": "em-1318",
            "modality": "actual",
            "framenet": "fn::Forming_relationships"
        },
        "arguments": [
            {
                "reo": "reo::Couple",
                "ere": "person",
                "entity": "ent-39",
                "entity-ner": "PER",
                "entity-specificity": "specific",
                "entity-text": "Brooks"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "event": {
            "reo": "reo::UNK",
            "ere": "transferownership",
            "lemma": "drop",
            "propbank": "UNK",
            "mentionid": "em-1871",
            "modality": "other",
            "framenet": "UNK"
        },
        "arguments": [
            {
                "reo": "UNK",
                "ere": "ere::Giver",
                "entity": "ent-102",
                "entity-ner": "ORG",
                "entity-specificity": "specific",
                "entity-text": "their"
            },
            {
                "reo": "UNK",
                "ere": "ere::Thing",
                "entity": "f-1896",
                "entity-ner": "commodity",
                "entity-specificity": "UNK",
                "entity-text": "UK newspaper holdings"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "event": {
            "reo": "reo::UNK",
            "ere": "transferownership",
            "lemma": "drop",
            "propbank": "UNK",
            "mentionid": "em-1901",
            "modality": "other",
            "framenet": "UNK"
        },
        "arguments": [
            {
                "reo": "UNK",
                "ere": "ere::Giver",
                "entity": "ent-102",
                "entity-ner": "ORG",
                "entity-specificity": "specific",
                "entity-text": "their"
            },
            {
                "reo": "UNK",
                "ere": "ere::Thing",
                "entity": "f-1926",
                "entity-ner": "commodity",
                "entity-specificity": "UNK",
                "entity-text": "UK newspaper holdings"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "event": {
            "reo": "reo::Give",
            "ere": "transfermoney",
            "lemma": "coughing up",
            "propbank": "coughing up.XX",
            "mentionid": "em-1929",
            "modality": "generic",
            "framenet": "fn::Surrendering_possession"
        },
        "arguments": [
            {
                "reo": "reo::Donor",
                "ere": "giver",
                "entity": "ent-1523",
                "entity-ner": "PER",
                "entity-specificity": "specific",
                "entity-text": "10M people in this country"
            },
            {
                "reo": "reo::Recipient",
                "ere": "recipient",
                "entity": "ent-102",
                "entity-ner": "ORG",
                "entity-specificity": "specific",
                "entity-text": "the business"
            },
            {
                "reo": "reo::place",
                "ere": "place",
                "entity": "ent-117",
                "entity-ner": "GPE",
                "entity-specificity": "specific",
                "entity-text": "this country"
            },
            {
                "reo": "reo::CostOrCotheme",
                "ere": "money",
                "entity": "f-2248",
                "entity-ner": "money",
                "entity-specificity": "UNK",
                "entity-text": "a minimum of £20"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "event": {
            "reo": "reo::Buy_sell",
            "ere": "transferownership",
            "lemma": "buy",
            "propbank": "buy.01",
            "mentionid": "em-1966",
            "modality": "generic",
            "framenet": "fn::Commerce_buy"
        },
        "arguments": [
            {
                "reo": "reo::Recipient",
                "ere": "recipient",
                "entity": "ent-1738",
                "entity-ner": "PER",
                "entity-specificity": "specific",
                "entity-text": "people"
            },
            {
                "reo": "reo::Donor",
                "ere": "giver",
                "entity": "ent-90",
                "entity-ner": "ORG",
                "entity-specificity": "specific",
                "entity-text": "The Sun"
            },
            {
                "reo": "reo::place",
                "ere": "place",
                "entity": "ent-117",
                "entity-ner": "GPE",
                "entity-specificity": "specific",
                "entity-text": "a country where people buy a newspaper that saw fit to print the story"
            },
            {
                "reo": "reo::Theme",
                "ere": "thing",
                "entity": "f-2116",
                "entity-ner": "commodity",
                "entity-specificity": "UNK",
                "entity-text": "a newspaper that saw fit to print the story"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "event": {
            "reo": "reo::Buy_sell",
            "ere": "transferownership",
            "lemma": "buy",
            "propbank": "buy.01",
            "mentionid": "em-2063",
            "modality": "generic",
            "framenet": "fn::Commerce_buy"
        },
        "arguments": [
            {
                "reo": "reo::Donor",
                "ere": "giver",
                "entity": "ent-90",
                "entity-ner": "ORG",
                "entity-specificity": "specific",
                "entity-text": "The Sun"
            },
            {
                "reo": "reo::Recipient",
                "ere": "recipient",
                "entity": "ent-1738",
                "entity-ner": "PER",
                "entity-specificity": "specific",
                "entity-text": "people"
            },
            {
                "reo": "reo::place",
                "ere": "place",
                "entity": "ent-117",
                "entity-ner": "GPE",
                "entity-specificity": "specific",
                "entity-text": "a country where people buy a newspaper that saw fit to print the story"
            },
            {
                "reo": "reo::Theme",
                "ere": "thing",
                "entity": "f-2109",
                "entity-ner": "commodity",
                "entity-specificity": "UNK",
                "entity-text": "a newspaper that saw fit to print the story"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "event": {
            "reo": "reo::Statement",
            "ere": "contact",
            "lemma": "speaking",
            "propbank": "speak.04",
            "mentionid": "em-2010",
            "modality": "actual",
            "framenet": "fn::Telling"
        },
        "arguments": [
            {
                "reo": "reo::Agent",
                "ere": "entity",
                "entity": "ent-72",
                "entity-ner": "PER",
                "entity-specificity": "specific",
                "entity-text": "a source close to Gordon Brown at the time of the story"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "event": {
            "reo": "reo::Buy_sell",
            "ere": "transfermoney",
            "lemma": "buy",
            "propbank": "buy.01",
            "mentionid": "em-2119",
            "modality": "generic",
            "framenet": "fn::Commerce_buy"
        },
        "arguments": [
            {
                "reo": "reo::Donor",
                "ere": "giver",
                "entity": "ent-1738",
                "entity-ner": "PER",
                "entity-specificity": "specific",
                "entity-text": "people"
            },
            {
                "reo": "reo::Recipient",
                "ere": "recipient",
                "entity": "ent-90",
                "entity-ner": "ORG",
                "entity-specificity": "specific",
                "entity-text": "The Sun"
            },
            {
                "reo": "reo::place",
                "ere": "place",
                "entity": "ent-117",
                "entity-ner": "GPE",
                "entity-specificity": "specific",
                "entity-text": "a country where people buy a newspaper that saw fit to print the story"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "event": {
            "reo": "reo::Buy_sell",
            "ere": "transfermoney",
            "lemma": "buy",
            "propbank": "buy.01",
            "mentionid": "em-2156",
            "modality": "generic",
            "framenet": "fn::Commerce_buy"
        },
        "arguments": [
            {
                "reo": "reo::Donor",
                "ere": "giver",
                "entity": "ent-1738",
                "entity-ner": "PER",
                "entity-specificity": "specific",
                "entity-text": "people"
            },
            {
                "reo": "reo::Recipient",
                "ere": "recipient",
                "entity": "ent-90",
                "entity-ner": "ORG",
                "entity-specificity": "specific",
                "entity-text": "The Sun"
            },
            {
                "reo": "reo::place",
                "ere": "place",
                "entity": "ent-117",
                "entity-ner": "GPE",
                "entity-specificity": "specific",
                "entity-text": "a country where people buy a newspaper that saw fit to print the story"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "event": {
            "reo": "reo::Lecture",
            "ere": "broadcast",
            "lemma": "leaked",
            "propbank": "leaked.XX",
            "mentionid": "em-2191",
            "modality": "other",
            "framenet": "fn::Speak_on_topic"
        },
        "arguments": [
            {
                "reo": "reo::Audience",
                "ere": "entity",
                "entity": "ent-1403",
                "entity-ner": "PER",
                "entity-specificity": "specific",
                "entity-text": "a \"friend\""
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "event": {
            "reo": "reo::Statement",
            "ere": "contact",
            "lemma": "told",
            "propbank": "tell.01",
            "mentionid": "em-2214",
            "modality": "actual",
            "framenet": "fn::Telling"
        },
        "arguments": [
            {
                "reo": "reo::Agent",
                "ere": "entity",
                "entity": "ent-81",
                "entity-ner": "PER",
                "entity-specificity": "specific",
                "entity-text": "Brown's communications team"
            }
        ]
    }
]