[
    {
        "event": {
            "reo": "reo::Accompanied_directed_caused_change_location",
            "ere": "transportartifact",
            "lemma": "blasted off",
            "propbank": "blasted off.XX",
            "mentionid": "em-1039",
            "modality": "actual",
            "framenet": "fn::Bringing"
        },
        "arguments": [
            {
                "reo": "reo::AccompaniedTheme",
                "ere": "artifact",
                "entity": "f-1056",
                "entity-ner": "vehicle",
                "entity-specificity": "UNK",
                "entity-text": "The lunar probe, aboard a Long March-3B carrier rocket"
            },
            {
                "reo": "reo::Initial_Location",
                "ere": "origin",
                "entity": "ent-99",
                "entity-ner": "FAC",
                "entity-specificity": "specificIndividual",
                "entity-text": "Xichang Satellite Launch Center"
            },
            {
                "reo": "reo::time",
                "ere": "time",
                "entity": "f-1071",
                "entity-ner": "time",
                "entity-specificity": "UNK",
                "entity-text": "Monday"
            },
            {
                "reo": "reo::ModeOfTransportation",
                "ere": "instrument",
                "entity": "f-1280",
                "entity-ner": "vehicle",
                "entity-specificity": "UNK",
                "entity-text": "a Long March-3B carrier rocket"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "event": {
            "reo": "reo::UNK",
            "ere": "artifact",
            "lemma": "made",
            "propbank": "UNK",
            "mentionid": "em-1515",
            "modality": "actual",
            "framenet": "UNK"
        },
        "arguments": [
            {
                "reo": "UNK",
                "ere": "ere::Agent",
                "entity": "ent-8",
                "entity-ner": "GPE",
                "entity-specificity": "specificIndividual",
                "entity-text": "China"
            },
            {
                "reo": "UNK",
                "ere": "ere::Artifact",
                "entity": "f-1540",
                "entity-ner": "vehicle",
                "entity-specificity": "UNK",
                "entity-text": "China's first man-made asteroid"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "event": {
            "reo": "reo::UNK",
            "ere": "transportartifact",
            "lemma": "land",
            "propbank": "UNK",
            "mentionid": "em-1626",
            "modality": "other",
            "framenet": "UNK"
        },
        "arguments": [
            {
                "reo": "UNK",
                "ere": "ere::Agent",
                "entity": "ent-8",
                "entity-ner": "GPE",
                "entity-specificity": "specificIndividual",
                "entity-text": "China"
            },
            {
                "reo": "UNK",
                "ere": "ere::Artifact",
                "entity": "f-1651",
                "entity-ner": "vehicle",
                "entity-specificity": "UNK",
                "entity-text": "a moon rover"
            },
            {
                "reo": "UNK",
                "ere": "ere::Destination",
                "entity": "ent-30",
                "entity-ner": "LOC",
                "entity-specificity": "specificIndividual",
                "entity-text": "moon"
            },
            {
                "reo": "UNK",
                "ere": "ere::Time",
                "entity": "f-1665",
                "entity-ner": "time",
                "entity-specificity": "UNK",
                "entity-text": "2017"
            },
            {
                "reo": "UNK",
                "ere": "ere::Instrument",
                "entity": "f-2204",
                "entity-ner": "vehicle",
                "entity-specificity": "UNK",
                "entity-text": "a lunar probe"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "event": {
            "reo": "reo::Send",
            "ere": "transportperson",
            "lemma": "sent",
            "propbank": "send.01",
            "mentionid": "em-1764",
            "modality": "actual",
            "framenet": "fn::Sending"
        },
        "arguments": [
            {
                "reo": "reo::Agent",
                "ere": "agent",
                "entity": "ent-8",
                "entity-ner": "GPE",
                "entity-specificity": "specificIndividual",
                "entity-text": "China"
            },
            {
                "reo": "reo::Theme",
                "ere": "person",
                "entity": "ent-531",
                "entity-ner": "PER",
                "entity-specificity": "specificIndividual",
                "entity-text": "its first astronaut"
            },
            {
                "reo": "reo::Recipient",
                "ere": "destination",
                "entity": "ent-348",
                "entity-ner": "LOC",
                "entity-specificity": "specificIndeterminate",
                "entity-text": "space"
            },
            {
                "reo": "reo::time",
                "ere": "time",
                "entity": "f-1803",
                "entity-ner": "time",
                "entity-specificity": "UNK",
                "entity-text": "2003"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "event": {
            "reo": "reo::Intrinsic_change_location",
            "ere": "transportperson",
            "lemma": "travel",
            "propbank": "travel.01",
            "mentionid": "em-1836",
            "modality": "actual",
            "framenet": "UNK"
        },
        "arguments": [
            {
                "reo": "reo::Mover",
                "ere": "agent",
                "entity": "ent-168",
                "entity-ner": "GPE",
                "entity-specificity": "specificIndividual",
                "entity-text": "Russia"
            },
            {
                "reo": "reo::Destination",
                "ere": "destination",
                "entity": "ent-348",
                "entity-ner": "LOC",
                "entity-specificity": "specificIndeterminate",
                "entity-text": "space"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "event": {
            "reo": "reo::Intrinsic_change_location",
            "ere": "transportperson",
            "lemma": "travel",
            "propbank": "travel.01",
            "mentionid": "em-1866",
            "modality": "actual",
            "framenet": "UNK"
        },
        "arguments": [
            {
                "reo": "reo::Mover",
                "ere": "agent",
                "entity": "ent-159",
                "entity-ner": "GPE",
                "entity-specificity": "specificIndividual",
                "entity-text": "United States"
            },
            {
                "reo": "reo::Destination",
                "ere": "destination",
                "entity": "ent-348",
                "entity-ner": "LOC",
                "entity-specificity": "specificIndeterminate",
                "entity-text": "space"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "event": {
            "reo": "reo::Send",
            "ere": "transportperson",
            "lemma": "sent",
            "propbank": "send.01",
            "mentionid": "em-1938",
            "modality": "actual",
            "framenet": "fn::Sending"
        },
        "arguments": [
            {
                "reo": "reo::Agent",
                "ere": "agent",
                "entity": "ent-159",
                "entity-ner": "GPE",
                "entity-specificity": "specificIndividual",
                "entity-text": "United States"
            },
            {
                "reo": "reo::Theme",
                "ere": "person",
                "entity": "ent-612",
                "entity-ner": "PER",
                "entity-specificity": "specificGroup",
                "entity-text": "human beings"
            },
            {
                "reo": "reo::Recipient",
                "ere": "destination",
                "entity": "ent-30",
                "entity-ner": "LOC",
                "entity-specificity": "specificIndividual",
                "entity-text": "moon"
            },
            {
                "reo": "reo::time",
                "ere": "time",
                "entity": "f-1977",
                "entity-ner": "time",
                "entity-specificity": "UNK",
                "entity-text": "1969"
            }
        ]
    },
