[
    {
        "event": {
            "reo": "reo::Firing",
            "ere": "endposition",
            "lemma": "former",
            "propbank": "former.XX",
            "mentionid": "em-1202",
            "modality": "actual",
            "framenet": "fn::Firing"
        },
        "arguments": [
            {
                "reo": "reo::Position",
                "ere": "position",
                "entity": "f-1219",
                "entity-ner": "title",
                "entity-specificity": "UNK",
                "entity-text": "minister"
            },
            {
                "reo": "reo::Employer",
                "ere": "entity",
                "entity": "ent-964",
                "entity-ner": "ORG",
                "entity-specificity": "specific",
                "entity-text": "defense"
            },
            {
                "reo": "reo::Employee",
                "ere": "person",
                "entity": "ent-8",
                "entity-ner": "PER",
                "entity-specificity": "specific",
                "entity-text": "a former defense minister"
            },
            {
                "reo": "reo::place",
                "ere": "place",
                "entity": "ent-53",
                "entity-ner": "GPE",
                "entity-specificity": "specific",
                "entity-text": "Greece"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "event": {
            "reo": "reo::End_position_with_organization",
            "ere": "endposition",
            "lemma": "between",
            "propbank": "between.XX",
            "mentionid": "em-1376",
            "modality": "actual",
            "framenet": "fn::Quitting"
        },
        "arguments": [
            {
                "reo": "reo::Employer",
                "ere": "entity",
                "entity": "ent-964",
                "entity-ner": "ORG",
                "entity-specificity": "specific",
                "entity-text": "defense"
            },
            {
                "reo": "reo::Employee",
                "ere": "person",
                "entity": "ent-8",
                "entity-ner": "PER",
                "entity-specificity": "specific",
                "entity-text": "his"
            },
            {
                "reo": "reo::Position",
                "ere": "position",
                "entity": "f-1408",
                "entity-ner": "title",
                "entity-specificity": "UNK",
                "entity-text": "minister"
            },
            {
                "reo": "reo::time",
                "ere": "time",
                "entity": "f-1415",
                "entity-ner": "time",
                "entity-specificity": "UNK",
                "entity-text": "2001"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "event": {
            "reo": "reo::Prosecute",
            "ere": "trialhearing",
            "lemma": "TRIAL",
            "propbank": "try.02",
            "mentionid": "em-974",
            "modality": "actual",
            "framenet": "fn::Trial"
        },
        "arguments": [
            {
                "reo": "reo::Defendant",
                "ere": "defendant",
                "entity": "ent-8",
                "entity-ner": "PER",
                "entity-specificity": "specific",
                "entity-text": "EX-DEFENSE MINISTER"
            },
            {
                "reo": "reo::CrimeOrCause",
                "ere": "crime",
                "entity": "f-999",
                "entity-ner": "crime",
                "entity-specificity": "UNK",
                "entity-text": "CORRUPTION"
            },
            {
                "reo": "reo::place",
                "ere": "place",
                "entity": "ent-53",
                "entity-ner": "GPE",
                "entity-specificity": "specific",
                "entity-text": "GREEK"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "event": {
            "reo": "reo::Prosecute",
            "ere": "trialhearing",
            "lemma": "trial",
            "propbank": "try.02",
            "mentionid": "em-1011",
            "modality": "actual",
            "framenet": "fn::Trial"
        },
        "arguments": [
            {
                "reo": "reo::Defendant",
                "ere": "defendant",
                "entity": "ent-8",
                "entity-ner": "PER",
                "entity-specificity": "specific",
                "entity-text": "a politician"
            },
            {
                "reo": "reo::CrimeOrCause",
                "ere": "crime",
                "entity": "f-1161",
                "entity-ner": "crime",
                "entity-specificity": "UNK",
                "entity-text": "setting up a complex money laundering network to cover the trail of millions of euros in bribes"
            },
            {
                "reo": "reo::place",
                "ere": "place",
                "entity": "ent-62",
                "entity-ner": "GPE",
                "entity-specificity": "specific",
                "entity-text": "here"
            },
            {
                "reo": "reo::time",
                "ere": "time",
                "entity": "f-1178",
                "entity-ner": "time",
                "entity-specificity": "UNK",
                "entity-text": "Monday"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "event": {
            "reo": "reo::UNK",
            "ere": "trialhearing",
            "lemma": "prosecution",
            "propbank": "UNK",
            "mentionid": "em-1714",
            "modality": "actual",
            "framenet": "UNK"
        },
        "arguments": [
            {
                "reo": "UNK",
                "ere": "ere::Defendant",
                "entity": "ent-8",
                "entity-ner": "PER",
                "entity-specificity": "specific",
                "entity-text": "his"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "event": {
            "reo": "reo::Prosecute",
            "ere": "trialhearing",
            "lemma": "trial",
            "propbank": "try.02",
            "mentionid": "em-2029",
            "modality": "actual",
            "framenet": "fn::Trial"
        },
        "arguments": [
            {
                "reo": "reo::Defendant",
                "ere": "defendant",
                "entity": "ent-8",
                "entity-ner": "PER",
                "entity-specificity": "specific",
                "entity-text": "he most senior government official to stand trial since the former prime minister and Pasok founder, Andreas Papandreou, was acquitted in 1991 on charges of accepting bribes"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "event": {
            "reo": "reo::Charge",
            "ere": "chargeindict",
            "lemma": "accused",
            "propbank": "accuse.01",
            "mentionid": "em-1304",
            "modality": "actual",
            "framenet": "fn::Notification_of_charges"
        },
        "arguments": [
            {
                "reo": "reo::Defendant",
                "ere": "defendant",
                "entity": "ent-8",
                "entity-ner": "PER",
                "entity-specificity": "specific",
                "entity-text": "Tsochatzopoulos"
            },
            {
                "reo": "reo::CrimeOrCause",
                "ere": "crime",
                "entity": "f-1329",
                "entity-ner": "crime",
                "entity-specificity": "UNK",
                "entity-text": "using a network of offshore companies during his stint as defense minister between 1996 and 2001, and for several years after that, to siphon off millions of euros in bribes he is said to have taken in exchange for procurement contracts, including the purchase of a Russian missile defense system and German submarines"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "event": {
            "reo": "reo::Give",
            "ere": "transfermoney",
            "lemma": "bribes",
            "propbank": "bribe.01",
            "mentionid": "em-1274",
            "modality": "generic",
            "framenet": "UNK"
        },
        "arguments": [
            {
                "reo": "reo::Recipient",
                "ere": "recipient",
                "entity": "ent-8",
                "entity-ner": "PER",
                "entity-specificity": "specific",
                "entity-text": "Akis Tsochatzopoulos"
            },
            {
                "reo": "reo::CostOrCotheme",
                "ere": "money",
                "entity": "f-1299",
                "entity-ner": "money",
                "entity-specificity": "UNK",
                "entity-text": "millions of euros"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "event": {
            "reo": "reo::Give",
            "ere": "transfermoney",
            "lemma": "bribes",
            "propbank": "bribe.01",
            "mentionid": "em-1439",
            "modality": "other",
            "framenet": "UNK"
        },
        "arguments": [
            {
                "reo": "reo::Recipient",
                "ere": "recipient",
                "entity": "ent-8",
                "entity-ner": "PER",
                "entity-specificity": "specific",
                "entity-text": "he"
            },
            {
                "reo": "reo::CostOrCotheme",
                "ere": "money",
                "entity": "f-1464",
                "entity-ner": "money",
                "entity-specificity": "UNK",
                "entity-text": "millions of euros"
            },
            {
                "reo": "reo::time",
                "ere": "time",
                "entity": "f-1492",
                "entity-ner": "time",
                "entity-specificity": "UNK",
                "entity-text": "several years after that"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "event": {
            "reo": "reo::Hiring",
            "ere": "startposition",
            "lemma": "between",
            "propbank": "between.XX",
            "mentionid": "em-1332",
            "modality": "actual",
            "framenet": "fn::Hiring"
        },
        "arguments": [
            {
                "reo": "reo::Employee",
                "ere": "person",
                "entity": "ent-8",
                "entity-ner": "PER",
                "entity-specificity": "specific",
                "entity-text": "his"
            },
            {
                "reo": "reo::Employer",
                "ere": "entity",
                "entity": "ent-964",
                "entity-ner": "ORG",
                "entity-specificity": "specific",
                "entity-text": "defense"
            },
            {
                "reo": "reo::Position",
                "ere": "position",
                "entity": "f-1364",
                "entity-ner": "title",
                "entity-specificity": "UNK",
                "entity-text": "minister"
            },
            {
                "reo": "reo::time",
                "ere": "time",
                "entity": "f-1371",
                "entity-ner": "time",
                "entity-specificity": "UNK",
                "entity-text": "1996"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "event": {
            "reo": "reo::Buy_sell",
            "ere": "transferownership",
            "lemma": "purchase",
            "propbank": "purchase.01",
            "mentionid": "em-1495",
            "modality": "other",
            "framenet": "fn::Commerce_buy"
        },
        "arguments": [
            {
                "reo": "reo::Theme",
                "ere": "thing",
                "entity": "f-1512",
                "entity-ner": "weapon",
                "entity-specificity": "UNK",
                "entity-text": "Russian missile defense system"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "event": {
            "reo": "reo::Get",
            "ere": "transfermoney",
            "lemma": "received",
            "propbank": "receive.01",
            "mentionid": "em-1541",
            "modality": "actual",
            "framenet": "fn::Receiving"
        },
        "arguments": [
            {
                "reo": "reo::Recipient",
                "ere": "recipient",
                "entity": "ent-8",
                "entity-ner": "PER",
                "entity-specificity": "specific",
                "entity-text": "Tsochatzopoulos"
            },
            {
                "reo": "reo::CostOrCotheme",
                "ere": "money",
                "entity": "f-1573",
                "entity-ner": "money",
                "entity-specificity": "UNK",
                "entity-text": "$210 million"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "event": {
            "reo": "reo::Get",
            "ere": "transfermoney",
            "lemma": "worth",
            "propbank": "worth.XX",
            "mentionid": "em-1599",
            "modality": "actual",
            "framenet": "fn::Amassing"
        },
        "arguments": [
            {
                "reo": "reo::CostOrCotheme",
                "ere": "money",
                "entity": "f-1616",
                "entity-ner": "money",
                "entity-specificity": "UNK",
                "entity-text": "3 billion euros"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "event": {
            "reo": "reo::UNK",
            "ere": "startorg",
            "lemma": "founding",
            "propbank": "UNK",
            "mentionid": "em-1650",
            "modality": "actual",
            "framenet": "UNK"
        },
        "arguments": [
            {
                "reo": "UNK",
                "ere": "ere::Org",
                "entity": "ent-290",
                "entity-ner": "ORG",
                "entity-specificity": "specific",
                "entity-text": "the country’s once dominant socialist party"
            },
            {
                "reo": "UNK",
                "ere": "ere::Agent",
                "entity": "ent-8",
                "entity-ner": "PER",
                "entity-specificity": "specific",
                "entity-text": "a founding member of the country’s once dominant socialist party"
            },
            {
                "reo": "UNK",
                "ere": "ere::Place",
                "entity": "ent-53",
                "entity-ner": "GPE",
                "entity-specificity": "specific",
                "entity-text": "the country"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "event": {
            "reo": "reo::UNK",
            "ere": "startorg",
            "lemma": "founder",
            "propbank": "UNK",
            "mentionid": "em-2094",
            "modality": "actual",
            "framenet": "UNK"
        },
        "arguments": [
            {
                "reo": "UNK",
                "ere": "ere::Org",
                "entity": "ent-290",
                "entity-ner": "ORG",
                "entity-specificity": "specific",
                "entity-text": "Pasok"
            },
            {
                "reo": "UNK",
                "ere": "ere::Agent",
                "entity": "ent-422",
                "entity-ner": "PER",
                "entity-specificity": "specific",
                "entity-text": "the former prime minister and Pasok founder"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "event": {
            "reo": "reo::UNK",
            "ere": "sentence",
            "lemma": "sentence",
            "propbank": "UNK",
            "mentionid": "em-1735",
            "modality": "actual",
            "framenet": "UNK"
        },
        "arguments": [
            {
                "reo": "UNK",
                "ere": "ere::Adjudicator",
                "entity": "ent-95",
                "entity-ner": "ORG",
                "entity-specificity": "specific",
                "entity-text": "a court in Salonika"
            },
            {
                "reo": "UNK",
                "ere": "ere::Defendant",
                "entity": "ent-365",
                "entity-ner": "PER",
                "entity-specificity": "specific",
                "entity-text": "the former mayor"
            },
            {
                "reo": "UNK",
                "ere": "ere::Sentence",
                "entity": "f-1767",
                "entity-ner": "sentence",
                "entity-specificity": "UNK",
                "entity-text": "life in prison"
            },
            {
                "reo": "UNK",
                "ere": "ere::Crime",
                "entity": "f-1774",
                "entity-ner": "crime",
                "entity-specificity": "UNK",
                "entity-text": "embezzling at least 18 million euros from city coffers"
            },
            {
                "reo": "UNK",
                "ere": "ere::Place",
                "entity": "ent-350",
                "entity-ner": "GPE",
                "entity-specificity": "specific",
                "entity-text": "Salonika"
            },
            {
                "reo": "UNK",
                "ere": "ere::Time",
                "entity": "f-1788",
                "entity-ner": "time",
                "entity-specificity": "UNK",
                "entity-text": "February"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "event": {
            "reo": "reo::Verdict",
            "ere": "convict",
            "lemma": "convicted",
            "propbank": "convict.01",
            "mentionid": "em-1793",
            "modality": "actual",
            "framenet": "fn::Verdict"
        },
        "arguments": [
            {
                "reo": "reo::Adjudicator",
                "ere": "adjudicator",
                "entity": "ent-95",
                "entity-ner": "ORG",
                "entity-specificity": "specific",
                "entity-text": "a court in Salonika"
            },
            {
                "reo": "reo::Defendant",
                "ere": "defendant",
                "entity": "ent-365",
                "entity-ner": "PER",
                "entity-specificity": "specific",
                "entity-text": "the former mayor"
            },
            {
                "reo": "reo::CrimeOrCause",
                "ere": "crime",
                "entity": "f-1825",
                "entity-ner": "crime",
                "entity-specificity": "UNK",
                "entity-text": "embezzling at least 18 million euros from city coffers"
            },
            {
                "reo": "reo::place",
                "ere": "place",
                "entity": "ent-350",
                "entity-ner": "GPE",
                "entity-specificity": "specific",
                "entity-text": "Salonika"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "event": {
            "reo": "reo::Steal",
            "ere": "transfermoney",
            "lemma": "embezzling",
            "propbank": "embezzle.01",
            "mentionid": "em-1874",
            "modality": "actual",
            "framenet": "fn::Theft"
        },
        "arguments": [
            {
                "reo": "reo::Victim",
                "ere": "giver",
                "entity": "ent-350",
                "entity-ner": "GPE",
                "entity-specificity": "specific",
                "entity-text": "city"
            },
            {
                "reo": "reo::Agent",
                "ere": "recipient",
                "entity": "ent-365",
                "entity-ner": "PER",
                "entity-specificity": "specific",
                "entity-text": "Vassilis Papageorgopoulos"
            },
            {
                "reo": "reo::Theme",
                "ere": "money",
                "entity": "f-1906",
                "entity-ner": "money",
                "entity-specificity": "UNK",
                "entity-text": "18 million euros"
            },
            {
                "reo": "reo::place",
                "ere": "place",
                "entity": "ent-350",
                "entity-ner": "GPE",
                "entity-specificity": "specific",
                "entity-text": "city"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "event": {
            "reo": "reo::UNK",
            "ere": "chargeindict",
            "lemma": "charged",
            "propbank": "UNK",
            "mentionid": "em-1918",
            "modality": "other",
            "framenet": "UNK"
        },
        "arguments": [
            {
                "reo": "UNK",
                "ere": "ere::Defendant",
                "entity": "ent-386",
                "entity-ner": "PER",
                "entity-specificity": "specific",
                "entity-text": "more than 30 politicians"
            },
            {
                "reo": "UNK",
                "ere": "ere::Crime",
                "entity": "f-1950",
                "entity-ner": "crime",
                "entity-specificity": "UNK",
                "entity-text": "other crimes"
            },
            {
                "reo": "UNK",
                "ere": "ere::Prosecutor",
                "entity": "ent-269",
                "entity-ner": "PER",
                "entity-specificity": "specific",
                "entity-text": "the Greek authorities"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "event": {
            "reo": "reo::Verdict",
            "ere": "acquit",
            "lemma": "acquitted",
            "propbank": "acquit.01",
            "mentionid": "em-2122",
            "modality": "actual",
            "framenet": "fn::Verdict"
        },
        "arguments": [
            {
                "reo": "reo::Defendant",
                "ere": "defendant",
                "entity": "ent-422",
                "entity-ner": "PER",
                "entity-specificity": "specific",
                "entity-text": "Andreas Papandreou"
            },
            {
                "reo": "reo::Time",
                "ere": "time",
                "entity": "f-2147",
                "entity-ner": "time",
                "entity-specificity": "UNK",
                "entity-text": "1991"
            },
            {
                "reo": "reo::CrimeOrCause",
                "ere": "crime",
                "entity": "f-2154",
                "entity-ner": "crime",
                "entity-specificity": "UNK",
                "entity-text": "accepting bribes"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "event": {
            "reo": "reo::Give",
            "ere": "transfermoney",
            "lemma": "bribes",
            "propbank": "bribe.01",
            "mentionid": "em-2189",
            "modality": "other",
            "framenet": "UNK"
        },
        "arguments": [
            {
                "reo": "reo::Recipient",
                "ere": "recipient",
                "entity": "ent-422",
                "entity-ner": "PER",
                "entity-specificity": "specific",
                "entity-text": "Andreas Papandreou"
            }
        ]
    }
]